exampro.co.uk 2013-06-23

# Privacy Statement

**The purpose of this statement is to set out how we use your personal information. By accessing and using Doublestruck's Websites, or by supplying your personal information at an event, online, by email, telephone or on an application form, you agree to your personal data being processed by us in accordance with this statement, which forms part of the Doublestruck Terms and Conditions. Doublestruck abides by the eight Data Protection Act 1998 principles and it requires all those who supply or use this data to abide by those principles.**

Doublestruck reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time with or without prior notice. By providing Doublestruck with your contact information and by using the Doublestruck websites you agree to this policy.

* ## Collecting personal information

Doublestruck is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. When you subscribe to Doublestruck for one of its services, including the Websites, you will be asked to provide certain personal information, for example your name, address, email address or phone number. Doublestruck will store this data securely and hold it on computers or otherwise, and use it for the purposes outlined below.

* ## Use of personal information

Doublestruck collects personal data for the purposes of the provision of services, administration of staff, contractors and self-employed specialists, payment validations, including taking and processing payments, statistical analysis and market research.

Doublestruck only uses personal information within the context of the purposes outlined above and it will only keep the information as long as is necessary to support these purposes.

If you do not inform Doublestruck that you do not wish to receive marketing messages from Doublestruck then Doublestruck may send you, from time to time, messages to keep you informed of suitable products or services. Doublestruck will give you the opportunity of "opting out" of receiving such communications both when you give Doublestruck your information and with each marketing message Doublestruck may send you.

* ## Controlling access to personal information

Doublestruck will not pass on your details to any third party (other than agents working directly on our behalf and other members of the AQA group of companies) unless you give Doublestruck permission to do so or Doublestruck is required to do so by law.

* ## Storing your personal information

Doublestruck employs strict information security procedures to store and handle your information. We protect your information against unauthorised access, unlawful processing, and accidental loss, destruction and damage.

* ## Data Protection Act - requesting further information from Doublestruck

If you have had any dealings with Doublestruck it is possible that Doublestruck holds information about you as a 'data subject'.

You are entitled to ask Doublestruck to disclose the information that it holds about you and, on payment of a standard fee of £10, Doublestruck will share it with you within 40 days. You are entitled to ask Doublestruck to correct any inaccuracies in any of the data it holds about you.M

Please address your enquiry to Doublestruck using the contact form on the relevant Website.

* ## Payment

Credit and debit card payments are processed on Doublestruck's behalf by a third party. This means that your data may be held temporarily by a third party but this will be held solely on behalf of and under the control of Doublestruck.

* ## Links to third parties

The Doublestruck Website includes links to other third-party websites. Doublestruck is not responsible for the data protection and privacy policies, procedures or the content of these linked websites, or any viruses which may be contained in them. You should read the relevant statements that apply to those sites.

* ## Cookies

The Doublestruck Websites use small files called 'cookies' to help you access content and order materials. Session cookies are used to pass information you enter from one page to another when you place an order and when you log in to the application.

You can instruct your web browser to block all cookies or prompt you when a cookie makes a request, though it will disrupt your experience. To do so please see the relevant set of instructions:
